我又以為，時間走得快如飛
Could've sworn the moment just blew away
記憶散去，心也跟著一起碎
A heart breaks when memories go to waste
如此真實，
卻感覺如此詭異
And it's so real,
it's not the way I feel
你應該要知道，
我們已被刻進石頭
It's something you should know,
our names are marked in stone
除非你的靈魂已被套上－
But not if your soul is bound with-
－時間枷鎖
-time
我一這生中從未有過－
I've never been so lost in my-
－如此失落
-life
即使歲月穿梭我卻還－
Years rolling and I'll still be-
－仍然健在
-alive
還是很難接受我這副－
It's hard knowing that I will never-
－不死之軀
-die
只因靈魂已套上枷鎖
'Cause I know my soul's been bound with time
就算我每天都好好度過
Though I take advantage of every day
分秒必爭，我是怎樣都會輸
every second counts, it's a losing game
沒有終點，這不是我在幻想
And there's no end, it's not just in my head
永遠不能停歇，有些就得說再見
Forever on the line, and some get left behind
除非你的靈魂已被套上－
But not if your soul is bound with-
－時間枷鎖
-time
我一這生中從未有過－
I've never been so lost in my-
－如此失落
-life
即使歲月穿梭我卻還－
Years rolling and I'll still be-
－仍然健在
-alive
還是很難接受我這副－
It's hard knowing that I will never-
－不死之軀
-die
只因靈魂已套上枷鎖
'Cause I know my soul's been bound with time
沒想到我的時間線會缺少盡頭
Never knew that my timeline lacked an ending point
會缺少盡頭
Lacked an ending point
也許它會就這樣跟著我繼續走
I imagine it only gets longer as I go
我的靈魂已被套上－
My soul's been bound with-
－時間枷鎖
-time
我一這生中從未有過－
I've never been so lost in my-
－如此失落
-life
即使歲月穿梭我卻還－
Years rolling and I'll still be-
－仍然健在
-alive
還是很難接受我這副－
It's hard knowing that I will never-
－不死之軀
-die
只因靈魂已套上枷鎖...
'Cause I know my soul's been bound with time...
我的靈魂已套上枷鎖...
My soul's been bound with time...
我的靈魂已套上－－
My soul's been bound with--